RUBIELYN NACHOR

64 Northway Estate, Finglas, Dublin

M: 0831549929

• Rbnachor25@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rubielynnachor

SUMMARY

I am a 4th year student studying, Bachelor of Science (Hons) Degree in Computing, due to graduate on 2018, bringing more than 3 years in software design, development and integration. I have a knowledge of Java, C++, C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Networking, Visualization and Data collection. I work well under pressure and consistently meets deadlines and targets while delivering high quality work.

SKILLS

Technological Skills

Java, C++, C# JavaScript, UML, MySQL, ABAP, .Net development, Shell scripting, Operating Systems, NetBeans IDE, Visual Studio,IBM Rational Rhapsody, SQL, Cisco Packet Tracer, HTML, Notepad++, Tableau, Mongo DB, Microsoft Office including Excel and PowerPoint.

Basic Skills

Honest and hard-working individual who is eager to learn new skills, speaks fluent English and has the ability to work as part of a team or upon own initiative.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

2nd Year Project

Name: Computer parts online shopping

Functionality: Login, Register, Add customer, Add Product, Remove Product, Search product, and Make

Purchase.

Technology: MVC CRUD Framework.

Language: Java

Library: im4java-1.4.0-1.5

Project GitHub link: https://github.com/Rubielyn/2nd-Year-Project.git

3rd Year Projects

project 1

Name: Weight and Temperature convertion

Technology: Angular 2

Project link: https://bitbucket.org/x.

Work placement Research project Description: Analysis of company's organisational structure and key business processes, conduct analysis and investigation in order to gain a deeper insight into the brief, demonstrating knowledge, skills and expertise learned throughout the program.

WORK HISTORY

Support Engineer

SuccessFactors/HCM/CRM SAP Ireland Limited Citywest Business Campus, Dublin - 1012-1014, Citywest Business Campus, Kingswood Ave, Cheeverstown, Dublin 24 01/2017 - 08/2017

My role in SAP SuccessFactors is to deliver a high standard Continuous Quality Checks (CQCs) for SAP Cloud based customers to ensure a smooth production before their Go-Live, during their Go-Live, and after their Go-Live. To ensure a successful Go-Live my task is to monitor the customer's back-end system to make sure that they their system meet SAP SuccessFactors best practices. These services are performed in SAP's CQC Solution Manager and SAP Cloud Platform.

Sales Agent

Pair Mobile Ltd, Swords Pavillions, Co. Dublin

08/2015 - 01/2017

My role in Pair Mobile was to direct sales, manage stocks, customer care, liaising with technicians, updating handsets, achieving targets, and issuing solutions for customers who are having problems with their mobile phones.

Floor Staff

Austrian Embassy - Dublin, Dublin

07/2015 - 12/2015

My role in this part time job was to serve food, prepare food and welcome guests in a embassy get together.

Embroidery assistant

Caramba Limited - 97 – 119 Northway Estate, Dublin 11

This role in this job was to fold and pack orders. I also had to make sure that the orders are managed properly.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science: Computing

Institute of Technology Tallaght - Blessington Rd, Tallaght, Dublin 24, D24 FKT9

Current

Information Technology Tallaght, Tallaght, D24

2016 - 2017 3rd Year: Internship Passed, Algorithms & Data Structures B, Cloud Computing B, Advanced Databases B, Innovation B+, Operating System B, Web Application Development 3 B.

2015 - 2016 2nd Year: Software Development 4 B, Project B, Networking 2 B, Management Science B, Object Oriented Analysis & Design C+, Software Development 3 B-, Software Quality Assurance & Testing A, Networking 1 B+, Database Design & Programming B, Discrete Mathematics 2 A, Web Design & Development C.

2014 - 2015 1st Year: Statistics B Database Fundamentals B+, Operating System Fundamentals B, Software Development 1 B+, Learning to Learn B, Discrete Mathematics 1 A, Business & Information System B+, Interface Design B, Computer Architecture B.

GPA: 1st year 3.29

2nd year 2.96

3rd Year 3.00

Secondary Education 2009 – 2013

Scoil Dara Kilcock co.Kildare

Higher Levels: Biology B, Art B, French C, Home Economics B, English A Ordinary Level: Maths B

INTEREST

I have interests in working with developing mobile applications, I also have a high interest in machine learning where I am able to practice developing in python and raspberry pi, solving complex problems, and I am also passionate in art and farming.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• INTERESTS I have interests in working with devices, machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), solving problems, working in a team, Graphic designs, farming.

SKILLS

ABAP, business processes, C, C+, C++, cashier, Cisco, CQCs, Customer Care, Database Design, Direct sales, Engineer, fluent English, HTML, IBM, IDE, Information Technology, Java, JavaScript, Languages, legal, Linux, Mathematics 2, C#, Excel, Microsoft Office, 97, Powerpoint, Windows, Networking 1, Notepad, Object Oriented, Object Oriented Analysis, Operating Systems, DB, Programming, Quality, Quality Assurance, Research, Selling, SAP, Software Development 2, Software Development 3, SQL, System Analysis, UML, Visio, Visual Studio, Web Design

REFERENCES

REFERENCES: Danielle Carter Pair Mobile Store Manager, Pavilions SC, Co. Dublin Tel: 0851440131, Keith Burke SAP mentor (2017), 1012 – 1014 Kingswood Ave, Citywest Business Campus, Co. Dublin Email: keith.burke@sap.com,

Ashish Dubey SF Manager, 1012 – 1014 Kingswood Ave, Citywest Business Campus, Co. Dublin Email: ashish.dubey@sap.com.